Guide to the Robert G. Coleman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Robert G. Coleman papers
1951-1998
SC1245
Coleman, Robert G.
4.5 Linear feet
Teaching materials and photographic slides.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographic slides documenting geological expeditions and teaching materials from Geology 80.
Access Terms
Geology--California--Stanford.; Geology--Research.; Geology--Study and teaching (Higher)--California.; Geology.; Petroleum--Geology.; Slides.
Collection Contents
- Geology 80
  - Lectures, 1991; 7 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, 1)
  - Course material, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Lecture topics and reading material, 1991 (Box 1)
- Aerial photographs of Saudi Arabia, 1951, 1956 (Box 2)
- Photographic slides, 1976-1998
  - Mendelev Russian cruise, 1976 Jun-Aug (Box 3)
  - Cuba, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - Saudi Arabia, Red Sea (Box 4)
  - Oman, 1981-1990 (Box 4)